Franjo Dumanovsky

Junior Front-end developer

Github: https://github.com/quelorel

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/franjo-dumanovsky/

Tatijane Marinić 10430 Samobor (+385 91 3311 806) franjodumanovsky@gmail.com

Introduction

I am a junior front-end developer with expertise in languages such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React. I have a passion for creating user-friendly and visually appealing websites and web applications. I have experience working on a variety of projects, ranging from small business websites to medium sized projects and even mobile apps with react native. In addition to my technical skills, I also have strong communication and collaboration skills, making me a valuable asset to any team. I am excited to bring my skills and experience to a new opportunity and contribute to the success of the company. Thank you for considering my application.

Experience

Magićmarinac d.o.o. - Zagreb — Web developer

APRIL 2022 - NOVEMBER 2022

Creating and maintaining websites for clients using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, Wordpress. Fixing bugs on existing websites and redesigning content based on customer needs.

Hotel Posejdon - Vela Luka — Receptionist

JUNE 2021 - SEPTEMBER 2021

Greeting guests as they arrive at a hotel. Checking guests in and out, and giving them their room keys. Taking bookings (by telephone or email), preparing bills and taking payments.

Miltonia d.o.o. - Samobor — Sales, Marketing, Web Development

JULY 2019 - JUNE 2021

Managed the product development process from start to finish, effectively communicating the value of our products and services through online meetups, presenting solutions for client's needs. Made my first website for this company.

Skills

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, SCSS, JQuery, GSAP, Framer-Motion, Adobe XD/ Figma, Photoshop, Bootstrap, Wordpress, PHP, WooCommerce, Github, Git

Languages

Croatian, Polish, English

Education

OŠ Samobor

(2003.g-2011.g) - Stražnička ul. 14, 10430, Samobor

XIII. Gimnazija Zagreb

(2011.g - 2015.g) - Av. Većeslava Holjevca 17, 10010, Zagreb

Baltik d.o.o. - Samobor — Communication Manager

JUNE 2018 - JULY 2018

Communication with Hoteliers, and organization of trips for groups of guests

NVS Music Group - Pula — Administration & Translator

AUGUST 2019 - JULY 2019

Communication between staff employees, organization of shifts in Excel, translation between English and Croatian teams.